<form>
	<field>
		<label>Enabled</label>
		<id>general.enabled</id>
		<help><![CDATA[Enable Privoxy service.]]></help>
		<type>checkbox</type>
	</field>
	<field>
		<label>Instances</label>
		<id>general.instances</id>
		<help><![CDATA[Sets the maximum number of requests xinetd can handle at once.]]></help>
		<type>text</type>
	</field>
	<field>
		<label>Log Type</label>
		<id>general.logType</id>
		<help><![CDATA[Configures xinetd to use the authpriv log facility, which writes log entries to the /var/log/secure file. Adding a directive such as FILE /var/log/xinetdlog would create a custom log file called xinetdlog in the /var/log/ directory.
SYSLOG syslog_facility [syslog_level] 
The log output is sent to syslog at the specified facility. 
Possible facility names include: daemon, auth, authpriv, user, 
mail, lpr, news, uucp, ftp local0-7. Possible level names 
include: emerg, alert, crit, err, warning, notice, info, debug. 
If a level is not present, the messages will be recorded at the info level.

FILE file [soft_limit [hard_limit]] 
The log output is appended to file which will be created if it 
does not exist. Two limits on the size of the log file can be 
optionally specified. The first limit is a soft one; xinetd will 
log a message the first time this limit is exceeded (if xinetd 
logs to syslog, the message will be sent at the alert priority 
level). The second limit is a hard limit; xinetd will stop 
logging for the affected service (if the log file is a common log 
file, then more than one service may be affected) and will log a 
message about this (if xinetd logs to syslog, the message will be 
sent at the alert priority level). If a hard limit is not specified, 
it defaults to the soft limit increased by 1% but the extra size must 
be within the parameters LOG_EXTRA_MIN and LOG_EXTRA_MAX which default 
to 5K and 20K respectively (these constants are defined in xconfig.h). 
		]]></help>
		<type>text</type>
	</field>
	<field>
		<label>Log On Success</label>
		<id>general.logOnSuccess</id>
		<help><![CDATA[Configures xinetd to log if the connection is successful. By default, the remote host's IP address and the process ID of server processing the request are recorded.
Below is a list of some of the more commonly used logging options: 

DURATION — Logs the length of time the service is used by a remote system. 
EXIT — Logs the exit status or termination signal of the service. 
HOST — Logs the remote host's IP address. 
PID — Logs the process ID of the server receiving the request. 
USERID — Logs the remote user using the method defined in RFC 1413 for all multi-threaded stream services. 
TRAFFIC — logs the total bytes in and out for a redirected service.
		]]></help>
		<type>select_multiple</type>
	</field>
	<field>
		<label>Log On Failure</label>
		<id>general.logOnFailure</id>
		<help><![CDATA[Configures xinetd to log if there is a connection failure or if the connection is not allowed.
		Below is a list of some of the more commonly used logging options: 

ATTEMPT — Logs the fact that a failed attempt was made. 
HOST — Logs the remote host's IP address.  
USERID — Logs the remote user using the method defined in RFC 1413 for all multi-threaded stream services. 
		]]></help>
		<type>select_multiple</type>
	</field>
	<field>
		<label>Connexion Per Second</label>
		<id>general.cps</id>
		<help><![CDATA[Configures xinetd to allow no more than 25 connections per second to any given service. If this limit is reached, the service is retired for 30 seconds.]]></help>
		<type>text</type>
	</field>
</form>
